

Message

Моге...

# Elizabeth Rose · 3rd Developer at Bird Inc Contact info

### **About**

Experience in Project Management, Business Analysis, New Project Development, System Development Life Cycle, Analysis & Reporting and Problem Solving.

Specialties: Proficient in MS .NET Technologies, UML, J2ME, Java, mySQL, MS SQL Server, MS Access, PERL, PHP, HTML, Javascript, Visual Studio, Macromedia Dreamweaver, Microsoft FrontPage, VB, C#

# Experience

#### Developer

Bird Inc

Oct 2014 - present · 6 yrs 11 mos

#### Developer

The Clorox Company

Feb 2013 - Oct 2014 · 1 yr 8 mos

## Developer

North American Title

Jul 2012 - Jan 2013 · 6 mos

#### **Technical Writer**

Oracle

Aug 2009 - Jul 2012 · 2 yrs 11 mos

Show less experiences

#### Education

University of San Francisco

**BA, English** 2006 – 2009